Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 2-627, OV 868)
  - The John Gary Show
    - I ain't down yet (Box 393, 538)
    - I believe (Box 393, 538)
    - I can't believe (Box 393)
    - I hear music (Box 393, 538)
    - I love Paris (Box 393)
    - I'm all smiles (Box 394, 538)
    - I'm always chasing rainbows (Box 394)
    - I'm gonna live until I die (Box 394, 538)
    - Iddy biddy baby (Box 394)
    - If (Box 394, 538)
    - If ever I would leave (Box 394, 538)
    - If you leave me (Box 394, 538)
    - Impressions (Box 395, 539)
    - (Intro) Chad & Jeremy (Box 395, 539)
    - Irish eyes (Box 395, 539)
    - Irish production (section 1 & 2) (Box 395, 396, 539)
    - It's over (Box 397)
    - Italian playon (Box 397, 539)
    - Italian production (section 1 & 2) (Box 397-398, 539)
    - J. Byner spot (Box 399, 540)
    - Jamaica farewell (Box 399, 540)
    - Jehosophat (Box 399, 540)
    - Jules M. playoff (Box 399, 540)
    - Knees up Momma Brown (Box 399)
    - Let there be peace (Box 400)
    - A little bit of heaven (Box 540)
    - The lonely goatherd (Box 400, 540)
    - Look at that face (Box 400)
    - Love is a many splendored thing (Box 400, 540)
    - Love is just around the corner (Box 400, 540)
    - Lovely way to spend an evening (Box 400, 540)
    - Lover's concerto (Box 400, 540)
    - Mama look a boo boo (Box 401, 540)
    - Mame (Box 401, 540)
    - Maria tonight (Box 402, 540)
    - Matchmaker (Box 402, 540)
    - Memoirs of a king (Box 403, 541)
    - Mexican production (section 1 & 2) (Box 403, 541)
    - Michelle (Box 404, 541)
    - Minstrel production (Section 1 - 3) (Box 404-406, 541)
    - More (Box 406, 541)
    - Movie theme (Box 406, 541)
    - Nancy (Box 407)
    - New beautiful baby (Box 407)
    - A nightingale sang in Berkley Square (Box 407)
    - No arms can ever hold you (Box 407, 541)
    - O sole mio (Box 407)
    - Old MacDonald (Box 407, 408, 542)
    - On a day like today (Box 408, 542)
    - On a wonderful day (Box 408, 542)
    - On the street where you live (Box 408, 542)
    - Once upon a summer time (Box 408)
    - Once upon a time (Box 408)
    - Paris spot (Box 409, 410, 542)
    - Penny a pitch (Box 411)
    - A perfect day (Box 411, 542)
    - Please don't talk to me (Box 411)
    - Pops classics (Box 411, 542)
    - Pops classics playoff (reprise) (Box 411, 542)
    - Possum song (Box 411)
    - Prisoner of love (Box 411, 542)
    - Racing production (section 1 & 2) (Box 412, 413, 543)
    - Red rosy bush (Box 413, 543)
    - River medley (Box 414, 543)
    - Rock-a-bye baby playoff (Box 414, 543)
    - Rock-a-bye baby playon (Box 414, 543)
    - Shadow of your smile (Box 415, 544)
    - Shangri-la-lodge (Box 415)
    - She loves me (Box 415, 544)
    - Sitting on top of the world (Box 415, 544)
    - Sloop John B. (Box 415, 544)
    - Softly as I leave you (Box 416)
    - Somethings gotta give (Box 416, 544)
    - Somewhere (Box 416)
    - The song of the coo coo (Box 416, 544)
    - The sound of music (Box 416, 544)
    - Spiritual number (section 1 & 2) (Box 417, 418, 545)
    - State Fair (Section 1 & 2) (Box 418, 419, 545)
    - Strangers in the night (Box 419, 545)
    - Summer medley (Box 420, 546)
    - Sunrise sunset (Box 420, 546)
    - Take me in your arms (Box 421, 546)
    - A taste of honey (Box 421, 546)
    - Tea for two (ping pong) (Box 421, 546)
    - Ten girls ago (Box 421, 546)
    - Tender trap (Box 421, 546)
    - That old gang of mine (Box 421, 547)
    - These are the years (Box 421)
    - Think cool spot (Box 422, 547)
    - This is all I ask (Box 422)
    - This old house (Box 422)
    - Till the end of time (Box 422, 547)
    - Till there was you (Box 422)
    - Till we meet again (Box 422, 547)
    - Tim Conway playoff (Box 423, 547)
    - Time after time (Box 423, 547)
    - Tip of my fingers (Box 423)
    - To life (Box 423, 547)
    - Tonight we love (Box 423)
    - Toyland playoff (Box 423, 547)
    - Trolley song (Box 423, 547)
    - Try to remember (Box 423, 547)
    - Two different worlds (Box 424, 547)
    - Two medley (Box 424, 547)
    - Unchained melody (Box 424)
    - Warm & willing (Box 425, 548)
    - Wee you no come back again (Box 425)
    - Western production (Section 1 & 2) (Box 425, 426, 548)
    - Whale of a tale (Box 427, 548)
    - What does he see in her (Box 427)
    - What now my love (Box 427, 548)
    - Where would you be (Box 427, 548)
    - While we're young (Box 428, 548)
    - Wien Wien (Box 428, 549)
    - Will you remember (Box 428, 549)
    - Without a song (Box 428, 549)
    - Yellow bird (Box 429)
    - Yesterday (Box 429, 549)
    - You and the night (Box 429, 549)
    - You are (Box 429, 549)
    - You'll never walk alone (Box 429, 549)
    - You're gonna hear from me (Box 430, 549)
    - Younger than springtime (Box 430, 549)
  - Orchestral Arrangements
    Parts (boxes 447, 448, 450-490, 493-504) and score (boxes 511-533) arrangements from Decca and Columbia recordings, live performances, radio shows, and other occasions; some composed by Fine.
    - A policeman's lot is not a happy one, #15 (Box 447, 511)
    - Ac-cent-tchu-ate the positive, by Harold Arlen, lyric by Johnny Mercer (Box 447, 511)
    - African Johnny (Box 447, 511)
    - Afrikan song, #200 (Box 447)
    - Airy fairy pipers, #36 (Box 447)
    - All about you, #184 (Box 447, 511)
    - Anatole of Paris, #57 (Box 448, 511)
    - Ants (Box 511)
    - Aria, #23 (Box 448, 511)
    - Auld lang syne (Box 448, 511)
    - Babbit and bromide, #12 (Box 450, 511)
    - Babooshka, #89 (Box 450, 511)
    - Bali boogie, #100, by Sylvia Fine (Box 450, 451, 512)
    - Ballin' the Jack, #14, arr. by Johnny Green (Box 452, 512)
    - Bamboo di bamboo, #56 (Box 452, 512)
    - Banjo dance (Box 452, 512)
    - Barrel house boogie and the blues, #95, arr. Buddy Bremen (Box 452, 512)
    - Bathtub admiral (Box 452, 512)
    - Begin the beguine (Box 452, 513)
    - Bendemeer stream, #58 (Box 452, 513)
    - Bloop bleep, #92, by Frank Loesser, arr. William May (Box 452, 513)
    - Blow Gabriel blow (Box 453, 513)
    - Blue Skies, #32 (Box 453, 513)
    - Blues (Box 513)
    - C'est si bon, #71, by Henri Betti (Box 453, 514)
    - Candy kisses, #96 (Box 453, 514)
    - Cannon ball (Box 453, 514)
    - Carnival of Venice (Box 453, 514)
    - Carnival of Venice jazz (Box 453, 514)
    - Change style, #65 (Box 454, 514)
    - China nights (Box 454, 514)
    - Ciu ciu bella, by Sylvia Fine (Box 454, 514)
    - Civilization, #93 (Box 454, 514)
    - Colored kisses (Box 454, 514)
    - Commercial film (Box 454, 515)
    - Concerto for tongue and orchestra, #28 (Box 455, 515)
    - Confidentiality, #74 (Box 456, 515)
    - Conga, #20 (Box 456, 515)
    - Countess of Coney Island, #54 (Box 456, 515)
    - Court jester, #189, by Sylvia Fine (Box 456, 515)
    - Cowboy, arr. Vic Shoen (Box 457, 533)
    - The cowboy, #208, arr. Gus Levene (Box 457, 516)
    - Crazy Barbara (Box 457, 516)
    - Danny - Lucy parody duet (Box 458, 516)
    - Danny boy, #7, arr. Paul Sawtell (Box 458, 516)
    - Danny Kaye opening (Box 458, 516)
    - Danny Kaye overture (Box 458, 516)
    - Deenah (Box 516)
    - Delicatessen song, #82 (Box 459, 516)
    - Dem Bones, #106 (Box 516)
    - Dena's lullaby, #8, by Irving Graham (Box 459, 516)
    - Detective medley, #78 (Box 459, 516)
    - Diamonds (Box 459, 517)
    - Dinah, #11 (Box 460, 517)
    - Dixie (Box 460, 517)
    - The Dodgers (Box 460, 517)
    - Dolly brothers, #80 (Box 461, 517)
    - Don't marry that girl, #86 (Box 461, 517)
    - Don't tickle me (Box 461, 517)
    - Dreams come tumbling down, #164 (Box 461, 517)
    - The duke of plaza toro, #8A (Box 461, 517)
    - The Dunhills (Box 461, 517)
    - Eat, eat, eat, #168, by William Saroyan (Box 461, 517)
    - Eileen, #179, by Sylvia Fine and Max Liebman (Box 461, 517)
    - Fair Dinkum, #187 (Box 462, 517)
    - Fanfare & coronation song, #52 (Box 462, 518)
    - Farming, #26 (Box 462, 518)
    - Film opening #2 (Box 462, 518)
    - Finale, #70 (Box 462, 518)
    - Fish and chips, #75 (Box 463, 518)
    - The five pennies, #207 (Box 463, 518)
    - Flamenco, #177, by Johnny Green and Al Sendrey (Box 463, 518)
    - Fleas (Box 463, 518)
    - Folk songs (Box 463, 518)
    - French (Box 463, 519)
    - The frim fram sauce, #53, by Joe Ricardel and Redd Evans (Box 463, 519)
    - Front and center (Box 463, 519)
    - G.M. patter (Box 464, 519)
    - The girl with the three blue eyes, #61 (Box 464, 519)
    - Glory hallelujah twist, arr. Pete King (Box 465, 519)
    - Good King D (Box 464, 519)
    - Happy ending, #160 (Box 464, 519)
    - Happy times, #55, by Sylvia Fine, arr. Johnny Green (Box 464, 519)
    - Here's how a how-de-do (Box 466, 519)
    - Hot lips Pierre, by Larry Orenstein, arr. Jack Hayes (Box 466, 519)
    - How could you believe me, #154, by Burton Lane (Box 466, 520)
    - How how, #40 (Box 466, 520)
    - Huckleberry Finn, #43, by Burton Lane and Alan Jay Lerner (Box 466, 520)
    - Hula Lou, #111, by Milton Charles and Wayne King (Box 466, 520)
    - I am an is, #46, by David Rose (Box 467, 520)
    - I belong to Glasgow, #25 (Box 468, 520)
    - I got a song, #45 (Box 468, 520)
    - I got a song (The railroad song), #91 (Box 468, 520)
    - I left my hat in Haiti, #155 (Box 468, 520)
    - I like old people (Box 468, 520)
    - I live to love, #190 (Box 468, 520)
    - I love to rhyme, #59 (Box 468, 520)
    - I taut I taw a puddy-tat (Box 468, 520)
    - I'm five (Box 469, 520)
    - I'm hiding (Box 469, 520)
    - Icebox (Box 469, 521)
    - If you are anxious for to shine, #9 (Box 469, 521)
    - In love again, by Sylvia Fine (Box 469, 521)
    - In my neck of the woods, #180, by Al Hoffman and Dick Manning (Box 469, 521)
    - Inchworm (Box 469, 521)
    - Information please, #84 (Box 471, 521)
    - It ain't necessarily so, #16, arr. Johnny Thompson (Box 471, 521)
    - It is never too late (Box 471, 521)
    - It's a sin to tell a lie, #60 (Box 471, 521)
    - Jack & Jill, #104 (Box 472, 521)
    - January (Box 521)
    - Jennie Macoo, #197 (Box 472, 521)
    - Jenny, #10 (Box 471, 522)
    - Jingle jingle (Box 473, 522)
    - Jingle journey 1-3 (Box 473, 474, 522)
    - John W. Wells, #110 (Box 475, 522)
    - Johnny one-note, #79 (Box 475, 522)
    - The Judge's song, #34, by Sir. Arthur Sullivan, lyric by W.S. Gilbert (Box 475, 522)
    - Julius Caesar (Box 475, 522)
    - Just imagine (Box 475, 522)
    - Kaye - Horton, #76 (Box 476, 523)
    - Kent comm. (Box 476, 523)
    - Kismet (Box 523)
    - Knock on wood, #185 (Box 476, 523)
    - Korean, #39 (Box 476, 523)
    - La vie en rose (Box 477, 524)
    - Ladies, ladies (Box 477, 524)
    - Let's not talk about love, #21 (Box 477, 524)
    - Life could better not be, #191 (Box 477, 524)
    - The liddle fiddle, #101 (Box 477, 533)
    - The little child, #199, arr. Spencer (Box 478, 524)
    - The little white duck, #105, arr. Ken Darby (Box 478, 524)
    - Lobby number, #41, arr. Ray Heindorf (Box 479-80, 524)
    - Louis Armstrong entrance music (Box 478, 524)
    - Macnamara's band, #77 (Box 478, 524)
    - Mad Dogs and Englishmen, #13, by Noel Coward, lyric by Sylvia Fine; arr. Johnny Green (Box 478, 524)
    - Madam (Box 478, 524)
    - Mademoiselle de Paree, #166, by Paul Durand (Box 478, 524)
    - The maladjusted jester, #189 (Box 478, 524)
    - Matilda, #115 (Box 478, 524)
    - McHugh, #97 (Box 481, 533)
    - Medley - Hutton & Kaye, #68 (Box 481, 533)
    - Melody in 4 F, #33 (Box 481, 533)
    - Mendelssohn, #31 (Box 481, 533)
    - Minnie the Moocher, #38 (Box 482, 533)
    - Model of a modern major general, #24, arr. Paul Sawtell (Box 482, 525)
    - Molly Malone, #4 (Box 482, 525)
    - Mommy give me a drink (Box 482, 525)
    - Monahan, #183 (Box 482, 525)
    - The moon and I, #2, by Gilbert Sullivan, arr. Johnny Green (Box 483, 525)
    - The moon is blue, #182, by Sylvia Fine (Box 483, 525)
    - The moon is your pillow, #94 (Box 483, 526)
    - My heart knows a lovely song (The contact song), #195 (Box 483, 526)
    - My name is John Wellington Wells, #110, by Sir Arthur Sullivan lyrics by W.S. Gilbert (Box 526)
    - My ship, #29 (Box 483, 526)
    - The new baby (Box 484, 526)
    - Nightmare song, #37 (Box 484, 526)
    - No for an answer, #62 (Box 484, 526)
    - The no-where blues (Box 484, 526)
    - Ocean parkway, #99 (Box 484, 527)
    - Oh by jingo, #100 (Box 484, 527)
    - On the double, #209 (Box 485, 527)
    - On the Riviera, #159 (Box 485, 527)
    - One life to live, #22 (Box 485, 527)
    - Opener (Box 527)
    - Opening I (Box 485, 527)
    - Opera sequence (Box 485, 527)
    - Outfox the fox, #196 (Box 485, 527)
    - Pabst themes from Pabst Blue Ribbon Show, #1 (Box 486, 527)
    - Pass the basket, #192 (Box 486, 527)
    - Pavlova, #35 (Box 486, 527)
    - The peony bush, #73 (Box 486, 527)
    - Philadelphia (Box 486, 527)
    - Pigalle, #112, by Georges Ulmer (Box 487, 527)
    - Playing on the seesaw (Box 487, 527)
    - Pons Kaye medley (Box 487, 528)
    - Popo the Puppet, #57 (Box 528)
    - The Princess of pure delight, #15 (Box 488, 528)
    - The puddle (Box 488, 528)
    - Put-down time (Box 488, 528)
    - Railroad song, #91 (Box 488, 528)
    - Rating game (Box 488, 528)
    - Relax with me (Box 489, 528)
    - Rhapsody for unstrung tongue, #109, arr. David Raskin (Box 489, 528)
    - Rhythm, #27 (Box 489, 528)
    - Rhythm of a new romance, #159 (Box 489, 528)
    - Riley's daughter, #171 (Box 489, 528)
    - Roll call (Box 489, 528)
    - The saga of the flea, #206 (Box 490, 528)
    - Saints (Box 490, 528)
    - Santa Claus looks like my daddy, #170 (Box 490, 528)
    - Saturday night, #19, arr. Irving Sheniker (Box 490, 528)
    - Scat signature, #47 (Box 490, 528)
    - Shickfitz (Box 528)
    - Shoo fly pie, #85 (Box 493, 528)
    - Sililoquy for three heads, #176 (Box 529)
    - Sills and Kaye hoarse opera (Box 493, 529)
    - Sing a tropical song, #88 (Box 493, 529)
    - Some of these days, #67 (Box 494, 529)
    - Song of the plains, #18, arr. Paul Sawtell (Box 494, 529)
    - Song writers, #81 (Box 494, 529)
    - Songs without words, #194 (Box 494, 529)
    - South Rampart street (Box 494, 529)
    - Spiritual (Box 495, 529)
    - Spring finale (Box 495, 529)
    - St. Louis blues, #90, arr. Rudy Herman (Box 495, 529)
    - Stanislavsky, #48 (Box 495, 530)
    - The steam is on the beam, #66, by Johnny Green, lyric George Marion, Jr. (Box 496, 529)
    - The sting (Box 496, 530)
    - Story/fairy tale, #17 (Box 496, 530)
    - Sunshine, lollipops, and rainbows (Box 496, 530)
    - Surfers - then & now (Box 530)
    - Sweet Georgia (Box 497, 530)
    - Talent playhouse (Box 497, 530)
    - Tea for two, #108 (Box 497, 530)
    - Thank you, #98, by Ervin Drake and Jimmy Shirl (Box 497, 530)
    - The thank you letter (Box 497, 530)
    - There is a hole at the bottom of the sea, #174 (Box 498, 530)
    - There's a hole (Box 498, 530)
    - They call the wind Maria (Box 498, 530)
    - Things to forget, #83, by Sylvia Fine (Box 498, 529)
    - Thumbelina (Box 498, 530)
    - Tico-tico, #44 (Box 499, 531)
    - Time medley, #64 (Box 499, 531)
    - Tongue twisters, #169, by Roger Edens (Box 499, 531)
    - The triplets, #30 (Box 499, 531)
    - Tropical playoff (Box 500, 531)
    - Tschaikowsky, #113 (Box 500, 531)
    - Turn around (Box 500, 531)
    - TV scorings (Box 500, 533)
    - Two by two (Box 501, 531)
    - The ugly duckling (Box 501, 531)
    - Uncle pockets, #172 (Box 501, 531)
    - The walrus and the carpenter, #162, by Sammy Fain (Box 502, 531)
    - Wee Doch in Doris (Box 502, 531)
    - Wee you no come back (Box 531)
    - What more do you want, by John Whitney, Alex Kramer, Hy Zaret (Box 502, 531)
    - When my first old, old love I knew, #3, by Gilbert & Sullivan, arr. Ted Duncan (Box 502, 531)
    - When I was a lad, #102, by Arthur Sullivan, lyric W.S. Gilbert, arr. Sidney Cutner (Box 502, 531)
    - When you're lying awake, #37 (Box 502, 532)
    - Where walks my true love, #193 (Box 502, 532)
    - Who tells the ants, #205, by Larry Orenstein (Box 502, 532)
    - Wilhelmina, #72 (Box 503, 532)
    - Will-o-waley, #188 (Box 503, 532)
    - Wish I may, #81 (Box 503, 532)
    - Yankee Doodle blues, #103, arr. Johnny Green (Box 504, 533)
    - Yogi (Box 504, 532)
    - Yonuary, #186 (Box 504, 532)
    - You made me love you, #63 (Box 504, 532)
    - You're for me Mimi, #167 (Box 504, 532)
  - Film Scores
    Arrangements and printed music (boxes 444-446), some composed and co-written by Fine.
    Arranged alphabetically by film title and by song title therein.
    - The court jester. Sylvia Fine and Sammy Cahn (Box-folder 444/1)
      - Baby let me take you dreaming
      - My heart knows a lovely song
      - Pass the basket
    - The five pennies. Sylvia Fine (Box-folder 444/2)
      - Follow the leader
      - Good night - sleep tight
      - Lullaby in ragtime
      - When the saints go marching in
    - Hans Christian Andersen. Frank Loesser (Box-folder 444/3)
      - I'm Hans Christian Andersen
      - The inch worm
      - The king's new clothes
      - The ugly duckling
      - Wonderful Copenhagen
    - Happy times. Sylvia Fine and Johnny Green (Box 445)
      - Brodny, brodny
      - Drink gypsy
      - Lonely heart
      - Medicine show
      - Road songs
      - Yakov's commercial
    - Inspector General. Sylvia Fine (Box-folder 444/4)
      - Happy times
    - Knock on wood. Sylvia Fine and Victor Young (Box-folder 446/1)
      - A room full of guests
      - All about you
      - Auto radio gag
      - Ballet
      - Brodnick and Papinek
      - Chacun
      - Chase to the pub
      - The end of Brodnick
      - Gromek procures
      - Jerry's hotel room
      - Knock on wood
      - Love
      - Monahan-o-han
      - Plot complications
      - Prelude
      - Sanctuary at Langston's
      - The umbrella
    - On the double. Sylvia Fine (Box-folder 444/5)
      - Fan dance
    - On the Riviera. Sylvia Fine (Box-folder 444/6)
      - Rhythm of a new romance
    - Peter Pan. Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley (Box-folder 446/2)
      - By hook or crook
      - Mothers
      - The rotters hall of fame
      - They don't make 'em like me anymore
    - Two by two. Richard Rodgers and Martin Charnin (Broadway show) (Box-folder 446/3)
      - An old man
      - The covenant
      - Everything reprise
      - The gitka song
      - The golden ram
      - Hammer music
      - Hey girlie reprise
      - Incidental
      - Ninety again
      - Noah's entrance
      - Poppa know best
      - Put him away
      - Revelation
      - Something doesn't happen
      - Somewhere
      - Why me?
      - You
      - You got to have a rudder on the ark
    - Up in arms. Harold Arlen (Box-folder 444/7)
      - Tess's torch song
  - Sylvia Fine
    Lyrics (handwritten and typed), manuscripts, and printed music (boxes 443-444, 449, 470, 491-492, 505).
    Arranged by medium and alphabetically by title therein.
    - Lyrics (Box 449, 470, 491)
    - Manuscripts
      - African song (Box-folder 444/8)
      - Ciu ciu bella (Box-folder 505/1)
      - Delilah Jones (Box-folder 505/2)
      - Election day (Box-folder 505/3)
      - The five pennies (Box-folder 444/9)
      - Happy times (Box-folder 444/10)
      - ILGWU (Box-folder 505/4)
      - In love again (Box-folder 505/5)
      - Japanese song (ami ami) (Box-folder 444/11)
      - Korean song (Box-folder 444/12)
      - Lone ranger (Box-folder 444/13)
      - Man with the golden arm (Box-folder 505/6)
      - Midsummer madness (Box-folder 444/14)
      - Mine alone (Box-folder 444/15)
      - Molly-o (Box-folder 505/7)
      - New fanfare - lobby number (Box-folder 444/16)
      - Once there was music (Box-folder 444/17)
      - Only yesterday (Box-folder 444/18)
      - Rhyme (Box-folder 444/19)
      - Romeo and Juliet (Box-folder 505/8)
      - Stickfitz (Box-folder 505/9)
      - Triple mirror (Box-folder 505/10)
      - Waltzing Matilda (Box-folder 444/20)
      - Wee you no come back again (Box-folder 444/21)
      - Who tells the ants (Box-folder 444/22)
      - You gotta love everybody (Box-folder 505/11)
    - Printed Music
      - Fine, Sylvia
        - Ciu ciu bella. Holland: Chappell & Co., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Ciu ciu bella. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Ciu ciu bella. London: New World Pub. Ltd., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Las cincos monedas (The five pennies). Argentina: Ediciones Internacionales Fermata, 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - The five pennies. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - I cinque pennies (The five pennies). Milano: Edizioni Curci, 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - The five pennies. London: Chappell & Co. Ltd., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Millionare de cinq sous (The five pennies). Paris: Chappell, S.A., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Follow the leader. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Goodnight - sleep tight. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Goodnight - sleep tight. London: Chappell & Co. Ltd., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Goodnight et bonne nuit. Paris: Chappel, S.A., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Happy ending. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1951. (Box-folder 443/1)
        - I keep humming the tune (Box-folder 444/23)
        - I like Marie (Box-folder 444/24)
        - Laugh it off. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1955. (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Love me again (Box-folder 444/25)
        - Lullabye in ragtime. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Lullabye in ragtime. London: Chappell & Co. Ltd., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Berceuse en ragtime (Lullabye in ragtime). Paris: Chappell, S.A., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Lullaby in ragtime. Copenhagen: Imudico, 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Main title - golden arm (Box-folder 444/26)
        - On the double. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1961. (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Only yesterday (Box-folder 444/27)
        - Popo the puppet. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1950. (Box-folder 492/1)
        - Un generale e mezzo (On the double). Milano: Edizioni Curci, 1961., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Uncle pockets (Box-folder 444/28)
        - Yon-u-ary (Box-folder 444/29)
      - Fine, Sylvia and Elmer Bernstein
        - Delilah Jones. Argentina: Ediciones Internacionales Fermata, 1956. (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Delilah Jones. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1956. (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Delilah Jones. London: The Victoria Music Pub. Co. Ltd., 1956. (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Delilah Jones. Milano: Edizioni Curci, 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Dalilah (Delilah Jones). Paris: Chappell S.A., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Delilah Jones. Sao Paulo: Editores de Musica, 1956., 4 copies (Box-folder 443/1)
        - Main title theme. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/1, 492/2)
        - Main title theme. London: The Victoria Music Pub. Co. Ltd., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/2)
        - Theme aus der Mann mit dem goldenen Arm (Main title theme). Munchen: Chappell & Co., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/2)
        - Molly-o. Hollywood: Dena Music, Inc., 1955., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/2)
        - Molly-o. New York: Charles Hansen Music Corp., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/2)
        - Molly-o. Argentina: Ediciones Nacionales Fermata, 1955., 2 copies (Box-folder 443/2)
        - Molly-o. London: The Victoria Music Pub. Co. Ltd., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 492/2)